(Leonard:)...I'd just apologize for everything
so we could end up in bed.
This is a 100 percent
"sex is off the table" I'm sorry.
(Penny:)All right. Thank you. I'm sorry too.
(Leonard:)Just to be clear,
sex is off the table, right?
(Penny:)Way off.
(Leonard:)Maybe we're not ready to hang out
as friends.
(Penny:)I don't know. Up until the last part...
...I was enjoying take-charge Leonard
with a little backbone.
(Penny:)Picking the movie,
knowing what he wants, a little cocky.
- Really?
- Yeah.
(Leonard:)Well, then, I'm putting sex
back on the table.
(Leonard:)What do you think about that?
Hmm, maybe I Iike it.
(Leonard:)If that's what you like, I can be that guy.
I'll be anything you want me to be.
(Penny:)Good night, Leonard.
(Leonard:)I am such an asthmatic dumb-ass.
(Leonard:)I had a weird night.
(Sheldon:)Mine was great.
(Sheldon:)I'm going to be a mommy.